<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<comments>
  <purpose>
    The purpose of this document is to give a short description of this program and its current state. At the moment this program is not working.
  </purpose>
  <creation_date>December 27, 2013</creation_date>
  Unfortunately I was not able to implement many of the features that I had intended to, so some parts of this program are not working.
  This program was created a few years ago and I have not updated it since. It took me about two weeks to get to a working, usable state.
  The main issue with this program is that there was no API for interacting with the Borderlands Wiki, which made the results unreliable.
  When this did work, it worked most of the time and it would sometimes return a random string of HYML when something useful was expected.
  This was mainly due to the fact that the program works based on sending requests for entire pages to the Wiki. Essentially it builds a path
  to the specific webpage that the user is looking for on the Wiki and parses out the data that the user is interested in from the Wiki.
  Admittedly this is not the best approach, but an API was not available at the time this was created so making JSON or XML requests was
  out of the question unfortunately. 
  It shouldn't be too hard to fix this up, and if there were a cleaner, more reliable way of getting data from the Wiki then I would love to do
  that. But like I said, there is no API that I know of that can get the required data for this program.
  One of the primary functions for this program was to grab the data on the "legendary" items in the game since they were always unique.
  So to speed this up, the program actually starts by grabbing the page that lists all of the legendary items in both Borderlands 1 and 2
  and populates an array of BorderlandsItem objects (after navigating to the item's page and grabbing the necessary data) so that instead of having 
  to send a request to the Wiki every time the user wants to get data on a legendary item, it is all stored locally in this array for quick access. 
  Most often I found myself looking up legendary items, sothat's why this feature was added.
  I'm actually somewhat pround of my interface design on this one. It may not be the prettiest design, but I like it. So in order to give you a good
  look at it, I have commented out a line that is causing the program to not work.
  Also, you may do whatever you like with the source code.
</comments>